Finding Aid for the Pacific Palisades Property Owners Association Records LSC.0874
UCLA Library Special Collections
Pacific Palisades Property Owners Association records
circa 1960
UCLA Library Special Collections
Pacific Palisades Property Owners Association
LSC.0874
42.5 Linear Feet (82 boxes and 4 oversize rolls)
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of Pacific Palisades Property Owners Association, 2003.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9948714943606533
Scope and Content
Organizational and legal records of the Pacific Palisades Property Owners Association (PPPOA), including maps, drawings, plans, photographs, and audio recordings that were created and/or collected by its directors. The documents collected by PPPOA are from various sources, including Los Angeles area city governments, land developers, and other Southern California regional associations. The collection also contains a small number of the personal papers of Rubell Helgeson, who served on the board and as president of PPPOA from the 1970s through the 1990s.
Organization and Arrangement
The records have been organized into series according to the file names that were originally assigned by PPPOA. Folder titles are either file folder names assigned by PPPOA, or named according to the document contained in the folder. Folders and loose documents not assigned a folder title by PPPOA may also be grouped by decade and entitled "Miscellaneous documents." The records are arranged in the following series:
Area 4 Alternative School - Temescal Canyon.
Bowdoin Street Closure - Miscellaneous PPPOA Issues.
Brentwood Palisades Community Plan.
Castellamare.
Coastal Transportation Corridor Specific Plan - Impacts on Air Quality.
Escondido Canyon - Santa Monica Mountains.
Headlands Corporation cases.
Lancer - Waste - Waste Burning - Air Quality.
Los Angeles Citywide General Plan Framework.
Los Liones Acquisition - Mountains Recreation and Conservation Authority.
Maps.
Mountains Development - Watt / Lachman - Helgeson - Miscellaneous Issues.
Oil.
Park Acquisition - State ParkCampaign Information.
PCH Traffic - Malibu Land Use.
PPRA (Pacific Palisades Residents Association) Newsletter.
Prop R - Super Scooper Fire Fighting Plane.
Rustic Canyon.
Various Palisades Issues Helgeson.
View Point Park.
Village Specific Plan.
Homeowners' associations -- California -- Los Angeles -- Archives.; Pacific Palisades Property Owners Association -- Archives
- Headlands Corporation Cases
  - Art Snyder contributions., v.d. (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - TT 34334., v.d. (Box 1, Folder 3-4)
  - LRC - Annual report., 1979 December 31 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Phase I density checks., v.d. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - TT 31935 - EIR., 1977 August (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - TT 31935 - Public hearing re subdivision appeals., 1978 April 27 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - TT 32184 - EIR., 1982 August (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - PPRA vs. Headlands., 1978 December 18 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Coastal commission - Headlands vested rights - Headlands claim - PPPOA appeal., 1977 May 16 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - PPPOA miscellaneous old [documents]., v.d. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - TT 31935 - Headlands submittals to City re EIR & Phase II., v.d. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Deeds - Headlands to York/Lazard - York to State of California - Rivas to Headlands., 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Grant deeds - Garapito, St. Pk., York, Temescal ridge, Rivas to St. Pk., etc., 1968-1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Moody's., v.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Trust deed - Sunset, Lezard, Headlands Corporation & TI., 1964 October 1 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Op ed., v.d. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Old documents from Vic Boesen[?]., v.d. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Basin Builders - Golf course tract., v.d. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Phase II - EIR., 1976-1977 August (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - TT 31935 modified - History & submittals., 1980 November 13 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Vested rights - Case law., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - TT 31935 - PPPOA responses & other - EIR Phase II - Letters to City Council., v.d. (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
  - TT 31935 - Headlands coastal., v.d. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - State coastal transcripts - AMH/Headlands., v.d. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Gateway., v.d. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Coastal hearings notices., v.d. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - City agendas., v.d. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - TT 31935 - Headlands submissions to City Council as proposed findings of fact on approval., 1978 June 6 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Dedication by Headlands of 2100 acres to state land transfers - Photos., v.d. (Box 5, Folder 7-8)
  - Notebook., v.d. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - TT 41661., v.d. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - TT 31935 - Chronology of slope failures., 1983 May 23 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - State of California transcripts - Various statements of domestic stock corp - Articles of corporation., 1981 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - State of California transcripts - Statements of foreign corp - International mining corporation., v.d. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - PPPOA vs. Headlands - Answer and memorandum of points and authorities in opposition to petition. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Land & Leisure, Incorporated - Form 8-K., 1971 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Cal gate '83-'84., 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Sunspot [Sunset?] Potrero oxy land swap., v.d. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Potrero canyon., v.d. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - TT 32184., v.d. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - TT 31935 - City council hearing (transcript)., 1978 June 8 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - TT 31935 - City documents - Power station., v.d. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Phase II - Notes of hearings - Newsletters., v.d. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - PPPOA submissions to coastal commission - Other public submissions to coastal commission., v.d. (Box 7, Folder 4-5)
  - Newsclippings., v.d. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Palisades., v.d. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - California coastal commission - Headlands coastal - Exhibits., v.d. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - PPPOA - LRC Corporation filings., v.d. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - PPPOA - LRC Corporation SEC filings., v.d. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Lazard Freres & Company., v.d. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Split Rock Realty Corporation grants to Sunset., v.d. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Grant deeds - Residential Land Corp/Alphonzo Bell., v.d. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Lazard/Webb & Knapp transfers., 1960 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - TI reconveyance to Lazard of part of area 3 - Wodgin [?] termination., 1966 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Plan of exchange & agreement - CUC, DEL/Sunasco, Incorporated, Penn./Sunset, Cal., v.d. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Agreement - Santa Ynez Corporation, Del./PALAL Corporation, Cal., 1968 January 2 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Agreement - Lazard + dummies/Headland Prop with exhibits., 1968 January 2 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - TT 32184., v.d. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Dedications., v.d. (Box 9, Folder 10-11)
  - Calvary church., 1987 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous personal., n.d. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Los Angeles magazine., 1979 April (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - PPPOA/Headlands negotiations - Proposed settlement agreement., v.d. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - PPPOA board of directors meeting., 1981 May 2 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Sunset quitclaim to Headlands., 1968 January 12 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Shasta Financial Corp/Sunasco Inc., Penn/Headlands Company - Loan agreement., 1968 September 1 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - State of California vs. Headlands - Eminent domain - Portion area 3 - 329.589c (Parcel 1725)., [1960s] (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Lazard + TI/Headlands - Trust deed., 1969 July 15 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Deeds from 1960s - Apparently unrelated to Lazard/LRC., v.d. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Grant deeds to Sunset signed by 1966 SIPCO officers, 1966 August - Sunset quitclaim to Headlands, 1968., 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Grant deeds to various corps from Vollmers - D1079, p572., 1960 December (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Grant deeds - Vollmers to Lazard dummies, areas 2,3,4,7., 1960 December 20 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - SSI articles of incorp - SIPCO/SII merge., 1966 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Los Liones., n.d. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - LRC - 8K, card 1., 1973 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - LRC - Annual report (all), card 1., 1970 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - LRC - 10K parts 1-2, card 1., 1970 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - LRC - 10K parts 1-2, card 1., 1971 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - LRC - 10K parts 1-2, card 2., 1971 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - LRC - Annual report (partial)., 1972 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - LRC - 8K, card 1, item 4., 1972 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - LRC - 8K, card 1, item 7., 1972 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - LRC - 8K, card 2., 1972 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - LRC - Proxy, card 1., 1972 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - LRC - 8K, card 2., 1973 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - LRC - 8K, card 1, items 3 & 14., 1972 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - LRC - Registration card 1, file 1., 1969 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - LRC - Registration card 1, file 11., 1969 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - LRC - Registration card 2., 1969 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - LRC - Annual report, card 1., 1969 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - TT 30453 - Public hearing re subdivision appeals., 1978 April 27 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Four corp certifications., v.d. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - LRC - SEC., v.d. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - United National., 1980 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - LRC - Proxy., 1980 April (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - LRC - 10Q, May '80 - 8K, May '80 - Prospectus, May '80., 1980 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - United National offer to exchange., 1980 June 22 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - LRC - Sched 13E&D., 1980 October 17 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - TT 40432 - Watt overflow., v.d. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - TT 31935., 1981 March 21 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - TT 32184., 1981 March 20 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Dedications at Santa Ynez Canyon Park - Headlands Prop. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Palisades Highlands., v.d. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - TT 32184., v.d. (Box 12, Folder 5-6)
  - Playing field., n.d. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - TT 32184 - EIR., 1982 August (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - LRC - Annual report., 1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Park dedications., 1985 April 30 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Coastal work., v.d. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Calle Deborah Gates., v.d. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Cassette album, 12 tapes., v.d. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Moody's - Notes., v.d. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Land history - Land ownership., v.d. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - AMH + Headlands vs. California Coastal Commission/PPOA., 1979 November 1 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Notes., v.d. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper clippings & backround data re Headlands I., v.d. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - TT 31935 - PPPOA - Hist docs., v.d. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - JBM notes re Headlands., v.d. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Deeds., v.d. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Haves - PPPOA., v.d. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1969 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Permit amendments - AMH Corporation + Headlands., 1980 May 20 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Exhibit A to opening brief of PPPOA., 1975 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - TT 32184 - Hearing before the California State Legislative Senate Committee on Nat Resources & Wildlife., 1981 November 18 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Coastal act boundary., 1978 November 2 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - PPPOA vs. City, Headlands + AMH Corporation., 1979 March 23 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - 2nd Civil No 58581., v.d. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - TT 32184 - Headlands II., v.d. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1981 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Highland Homeowners - PPPOA communications., v.d. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Lazard Freres & Company - Directors., 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Lazard Freres & Company - Directors., 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Lazard Freres & Company - Directors., 1971-1973 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Water tanks for Headlands hearing., 1982 January 4 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - LRC & subsidiaries., n.d. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - LRC & subsidiaries - SEC., n.d. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - LRC & subsidiaries - Exhibits., n.d. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - LRC & subsidiaries - 8K., 1971 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - LRC & subsidiaries - Litigation (aircrash)., 1970 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Gateway tennis club., 1971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - TT 31070., 1969-1973 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Cal Hamilton re developer clients/Planning Department of Los Angeles - Photographs & negatives., v.d. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - TT 31072 - Headlands phase I., v.d. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - TT 32200., 1977 October (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - TT 34923 - Commercial tract., 1978-1980 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Lazard Freres & Company - Directors., 1968-1971 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - LRC - Registration papers., 1972 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Lazard Freres & Company - Directors., 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - LRC - Prospectus., 1979 June 15 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - United National Financial Corporation - 10K., 1979 December (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - LRC - 10Q., 1979 June 30 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - LRC - Sched 13E - Tender offer., 1980 August 22 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - LRC - 10K card 3., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - LRC - 10Q card 1., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - LRC - 10K card 1., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - LRC - 10K card 2., 1979 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - LRC - 10K card 1., 1976 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - LRC - 10K card 2., 1976 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - LRC - 10Q., 1979-1980 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - LRC - Sched 13D., 1979 October 15 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - LRC - 8K card 3., 1972 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - LRC - 10K card 1., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - LRC - 10K card 2., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - LRC - 10K card 3., 1973 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - TT 34923 & 31070 - Headlands phase I., 1976-1979 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Snyder campaign contributors, etc. - Conflict of interest Woodland Hills., v.d. (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
  - Condemnation as a tool for land acquisition for the state park system in the Santa Monica Mountains., 1992 November (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - PPPOA vs. City, Headlands + AMH Corporation - Opening brief of appellant PPPOA., 1980 August 18 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - PPPOA vs. City, Headlands + AMH Corporation - Request for judicial notice by petitioner - appellant PPPOA., 1981 February (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - PPPOA vs. City, Headlands + AMH Corporation - Appeal - Appellant's brief in reply to respondent's brief., 1981 March (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - PPPOA vs. City, Headlands + AMH Corporation - Appeal - Appellant's brief in reply to Headlands., 1981 February (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Gateway institutional., v.d. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - PPPOA vs. City, et al & Headlands - Petition for hearing for hearing before supreme court., 1981 August 24 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - PPPOA vs. City, et al & Headlands - Petition for rehearing on appeal from judgement of superior court., 1981 July 28 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Woodland Hills Residents vs. City of Los Angeles., 1977-1980 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Watt-Headland nixed [?] park dedication., v.d. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper clippings., v.d. (Box 21, Folder 1-3)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1982 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1983 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1984 (Box 22, Folder 3-4)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1985 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1986 July (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1986 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1987 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1988 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1989 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - TT 31070., v.d. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - TT 31935., v.d. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - TT 34923., v.d. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - TT 41661 & 41662., v.d. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - TT 32184., v.d. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - TT 32184., v.d. (Box 23, Folder 6-7)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1962 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1965 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1966 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1967 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1968 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1969 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1970 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1971 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1972 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1973 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1974 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1976 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1977 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1977 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1978 (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1979 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1981 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1991 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1992 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1993 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1995 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1996 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1997 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1998 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1999 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1990s (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous documents., n.d. (Box 27, Folder 1-4)
  - PPPOA - LRC settlement., 1982 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Traffic - newspaper clippings., 1978-1980 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Traffic., 1981 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Traffic - vehicle counts., v.d. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Calvary church., 1965-1987 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - LRC - 10K., 1977 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - LRC - Annual report card., 1976 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Maps of Highlands & Santa Monica Mountains. (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Amended coastal permit - Dedications documents., 1980 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - PPPOA legal documents - PPPOA vs. City of Los Angeles, et al., 1981 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - PPPOA legal documents., 1982-1984 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - TT 31935 - PPPOA legal documents., v.d. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - TT 31935 - Traffic study., 1978 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - TT 32184 - Hearing., 1981 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - TT 31935 - Public hearing re subdivision appeals - Brentwood - Pacific Palisades., 1978 April 27 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Traffic - PPPOA letters & reports., 1977-1980 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Traffic reports., 1976-1980 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - TT 32184 - Gateway - Draft EIR., 1982 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Traffic & air quality - City of Los Angeles reports & memos., 1975-1980 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Palisades Highlands - Claim of Exemption., 1977 April 15 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    General note
    Box 30 is an oversize flat box.
  - Plans - Palisades Highlands - Gateway - TT 32184., v.d. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    Container 31 is an oversize map folder.
  - Plans - Miscellaneous - TT 31935 - Preliminary parcel maps - Calvary church., v.d. (Box 32, Folder 1)
    Container 32 is an oversize map folder.
  - Playing fields., 1993 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - TT 31935 - Coastal appeals., 1970s & 1980s (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - TT 31935 - Appeal to city., 1978 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - TT 31935 - Public Hearing re Subdivision Appeals., 1978 (Box 79, Folder 10)
- Various Palisades Issues - Helgeson
  - Sunset pacific plaza development at Sunset PCH., 1983 August (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Palisades women's club., 1984 November (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Zone/yard variance 15442 W. Sunset Blvd., 1999 December (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence., 1970s & 1980s (Box 33, Folder 4-5)
  - Potrero canyon., 1982 July (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Potrero canyon - Final EIR., 1985 June (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Potrero canyon., 1980s (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Potrero canyon., 1984 October (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Potrero canyon., 1980s (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Palisades village center - 881 Alma Real Dr., 1979 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Haverford/Antioch condos., 1970s (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Kollsman vs. City of Los Angeles - Slope density., 1970s (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Kollsman vs. City of Los Angeles - Slope density., 1970s (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Las Pulgas Canyon issues - Marquette St., 1990s (Box 35, Folder 4-6)
  - PPRA general - EIR seminar., 1980s (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Quimby fees., 1970s (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - PPRA matters., 1970s & 1980s (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - 17474 Tramanto - Decision of Coastal Commission., 1980s (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - City parcel map ordinance., 1970s (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Cellular sites., 1990s (Box 36, Folder 6-7)
  - Coastal access information., 1980s (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - 1545 & 1462 Lachman Lane., 1990s (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - YMCA / Temescal., 1980s (Box 36, Folder 10-11)
  - Calvary church., 1980s (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Coastal issues / permits - Coastal Commission., 1970s (Box 37, Folder 2-3)
  - Hampton Place development - 73 lots., 1980s (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Hillside ordinance., 1990s (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Santa Monica Canyon development., 1987 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Santa Monica Mountains Comprehensive Plan., 1970s (Box 38, Folder 2-4)
  - Sunrise Assisted Living., 1990s (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Will Rogers - Sunset signalization - Sunset widening., 1990s (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Getty., 1990s & 2000s (Box 39, Folder 1-5)
  - Bel Air Bay Club expansion., 2000 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Bernheimer Gardens (Bay Club)., 1990s (Box 39, Folder 7)
- PCH Traffic - Malibu Land Use
  - PCH traffic issues., 1980s (Box 40, Folder 1-2)
  - PCH planning meeting., 1984 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - PCH study., 1984 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - PCH traffic issues., 1980s (Box 40, Folder 5-6)
  - Traffic., 1980s (Box 41, Folder 1-3)
  - Traffic study - J Paul Getty Museum, Santa Monica, Los Angeles., 1985 March (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Record of Division of Highways - Public mtg covering proposed improvements of PCH - vol.1., 1971 March 29 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Record of Division of Highways - Public mtg covering proposed improvements of PCH - vol.2., 1971 March 29 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Malibu Land Use plan., 1980s (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings., 1980s (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Malibu Land Use plan., 1980s (Box 43, Folder 1-4)
- Los Angeles Citywide General Plan Framework
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1990s (Box 44, Folder 1-3)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1990s (Box 45, Folder 1-2)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings., 1990s (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles City Planning Department Staff Report to City Planning Commission., n.d. (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Commentaries on Mayor Riordan's General Plan Framework - Introduced by PPRA., 1995 June (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Los Angeles Citywide General Plan Framework - Proposed Framework Element (annotated)., 1995 July (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1995-1997 (Box 46, Folder 1-3)
  - City of Los Angeles - Miscellaneous documents., 1995-1997 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Comments on draft EIR - Submitted by Pacific Palisades Community Council. (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Proposed City of Los Angeles General Plan Framework - Executive Summary., 1995 August (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Community Plan Update openhouse documents - West Los Angeles Community Plan., 1998 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles City Planning Department Staff Report to City Planning Commission., 1995 June (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Los Angeles housing stimulus package., 1980 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Transportation Improvement and Mitigation Program (annotated)., 1995 February (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Framwork Element Public Comments., 1995 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Draft EIR (annotated)., 1995 January (Box 48, Folder 1-3)
- Los Liones Acquisition - Mountains Recreation and Conservation Authority
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s & 1990s (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous newspaper clippings., v.d. (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Maps., v.d. (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - List of exhibits., n.d. (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - A history of Los Liones Canyon... by Rubell Helgeson., 1992 October; (2 copies) (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous documents., 1980s & 1990s (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Quitclaim Headland from Sunset Pet. 1966 - Transfer of Los Liones / Santa Ynez., 1966 & v.d. (Box 50, Folder 2)